Guide to the Sports Information Office: Photographic Negatives collection, circa 1924-1992, 1995, undated UA.13.02.0018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Football Negatives, circa 1924-1992; 1995; undated; 8
  - Groups, 29
    - Bob Matheson, Mike Shasby, unidentified players, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03421)
    - Andy Beath, [?], Bob Adams, Mark Caldwell, Chuck Drulis, Dave Dunaway, Todd Orvald, Scotty Glacken, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03422)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03423)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03424)
    - Seniors, unidentified, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03425)
    - Jay Calabrese, Dave Dunaway, Coach Tom Harp, Todd Orvald, Bob Foyle (spring practice), 1966 Feb. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03426)
    - Robin Bodkin, J. B. Edwards, Bob Lasky, Bob Foyle, Defensive Line Coach George Hill, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03427)
    - Bob Matheson, Mike Shasby, Coach Tom Harp, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03428)
    - Mike Murphy, Bob Foyle (co-captains), Coach Tom Harp, circa 1966-1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03429)
    - Bruce Wiesley, Roger Hayes, Bill Phipps, Defensive End Coach Herschel Caldwell, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03430)
    - John Alexander, Bucky Fondren, Mike Renneker, Carl Gersbach, Rodger Parker, Jerry Barringer, Bedford Cannon, Offensive Line Coach Harold Hunter, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03431)
    - Bob Matheson, Dave Dunaway, Mike Murphy, Jay Calabrese, Coach Tom Harp, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03432)
    - Al Woodall, Jake Devonshire, Jay Calabrese, Frank Ryan, Offensive Backfield Coach Jacque Hetrick, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03433)
    - Todd Orvald, Jake Devonshire, Jay Calabrese, Andy Beath, Offensive Backfield Coach Jacque Hetrick, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03434)
    - Al Woodall, Page Wilson, Frank Ryan, Ken Chatham, Ed Hicklin, Offensive Backfield Coach Jacque Hetrick, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03435)
    - Frank Ryan, Jake Devonshire, Jay Calabrese, Todd Orvald, Offensive Backfield Coahc Jacque Hetrick, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03436)
    - Todd Orvald, Al Woodall, Coach Tom Harp, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03437)
    - Dave Dunaway, Bob Matheson, Coach Tom Harp, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03438)
    - Ed Newman, Bob Matheson, Charles Grace, Linebackers Coach Carmen Falcone, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03439)
    - Jim Kidd, Mike Swomley, Dave Dunaway, Offensive End Coach Stan Crisson, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03440)
    - Coaching Staff (Tom Harp, Eddie Cameron, Wallace Wade, Bill Murray), 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03441)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03442)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1966 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03443)
    - Robin Bodkin, Bob Foyle, Bob Lasky, 1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03444)
    - Ed Hicklin, Larry Davis, Al Woodall, Jake Devonshire, Henley Carter, 1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03445)
    - Coach Tom Harp, Sonny Jurgenson, Dave Golden, Al Woodall, Larry Davis, 1967 May (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03446)
    - Larry Davis, Al Woodall, Coach Tom Harp, 1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03447)
    - Art Vann, Jay Calabrese, Coach Tom Harp, 1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03448)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, 1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03449)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, 1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03450)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, 1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03451)
    - Players, unidentified, 1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03452)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1967 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03453)
    - Fred Zirkle, Bob Hepler, Guy Johnson, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03454)
    - John Cappellano, Don Baglien, Leo Hart, Marcel Courtillet, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03455)
    - Marcel Courtillet, Dave Trice, Don Baglien, John Cappellano, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03456)
    - Phil Asack, Leo Hart, Wes Chesson, Marcel Courtillet, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03457)
    - Danny Rose, E. J. Jackson, Tom Edens, Bill McKee, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03458)
    - Marcel Courtillet, Mike Fitzpatrick, Dennis Cassidy, Ken Bombard, Frank Lilly, Bob Shinn, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03459)
    - Jim Dearth, Henley Carter, Tom Edens, Marcel Courtillet, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03460)
    - Ed Hicklin, Wes Chesson, Larry Davis, Phil Singer, 1968 Aug. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03461)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, unidentified, 1968 Sept. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03462)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, unidentified, 1968 Sept. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03463)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, unidentified, 1968 Sept. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03464)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, unidentified, 1968 Sept. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03465)
    - Coach George Hill, Bruce Mills, Andy Smith, David Gibbs, Bill Leonard (Freshman team), 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03466)
    - Coach Tom Harp, Leo Hart, Randy Short, Dave Trice, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03467)
    - Mike Lambros, Gary Rute, John Musselman, Coach Stan Crisson, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03468)
    - Dave Trice, Leo Hart, Coach Jimmy Poole, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03469)
    - Jim Musselman, Randy Stevenson, Coach George Hill, Mike Davies, Joe Sciulli, Ken Krueger, 1968 Aug. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03470)
    - Bob Fitch, Dick Biddle, Bob Zaleski, Coach Harold Hunter, 1968 Aug. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03471)
    - David Pugh, Coach Herschel Caldwell, L. G. Bryant, 1968 Aug. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03472)
    - Coach Hal Hunter, Dennis Satyshur, Don Gunter, Joe Tinko, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03473)
    - Henley Carter, Earl Mowry, Dave Trice, Coach Herschel Caldwell, Rusty McDow, 1968 Aug. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03474)
    - Bo Bochow, Rich Searl, Coach Stan Crisson, Joe Compitello, Dixie Abdella, Coach Sam Timer, John Dull, Coach Jacque Hetrick, 1968 Aug. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03475)
    - Steve Thompson, Don Gunter, Joe Tinko, Gay Guthrie, Daryl Fox, Coach Harold Hunter, John Cappellano, George Joseph, Art Bosetti, Lanny Murdock, Tom Cain, Bob Hepler, Ken Homa, 1968 Aug. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03476)
    - Coach Sam Timer, John Dull, Rich Searl, Dixie Abdella, Mike Hayes, 1968 Aug. (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03477)
    - Coach Jacque Hetrick, Randy Short, Jim Madden, Jim Tomanchek, Jim Forbis, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03478)
    - Coach Harold Hunter, John Johnston, Dennis Satyshur, Jerry Giffin, Steve Thompson, John Cappellano, Don Gunter, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03479)
    - Henley Carter, Fred Zirkle, Larry Davis, J. B. Edwards, Coach Tom Harp, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03480)
    - Jack Hall, Dick Havens, Jimmy Poole, Herb Goins (Freshman team), 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03481)
    - Hal Hunter, Herschel Caldwell, Carmen Falcone, Sam Timer, Stan Crisson, George Hill, Jacque Hetrick, Jack Hall, Dick Havens, Bob Cox, Tom Harp, Jimmy Poole, Herb Goins, John Gutekunst, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03482)
    - Hal Hunter, Herschel Caldwell, Carmen Falcone, Sam Timer, Stan Crisson, Jacque Hetrick, Jack Hall, Bob Cox, Tom Harp, George Hill, John Gutekunst, 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03483)
    - Trainers (Otho Davis, Roy Gilchrist, Max Crowder), 1968 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03484)
    - Phil Asack, Don Baglien, Richard Searl, Mike Davies, Leo Hart, Wes Chesson, Ernest Jackson, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03485)
    - Dick Biddle, Joe Campitello, Ken Bombard, Don Gunter, Bruce Mills, Joe Sciulli, Robert Shinn, Bob Hepler, Wes Chesson, Jim Dearth, Chris Hill, Gene Debolt, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03486)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03487)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03488)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03489)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03490)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03491)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03492)
    - Rich Searl, Dave Trice, Ernie Jackson, Mike Davies, Bob Zwirko, Bob Hepler, Guy Johnson, Jim Dearth, Wes Chesson, Bob Hepler, Marcel Courtillet, Leo Hart, Dennis Satyshur, Coach Tom Harp, circa 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03493)
    - Art Bosetti, Lanny Murdock, Bob Hepler, Coach Harold Hunter, Gay Guthrie, Tom Cain, Daryl Fox, circa 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03494)
    - Jacque Hetrick, Sam Timer, Carmen Falcone, John Gutekunst, Alex Gibbs, Hal Hunter, Stan Crisson, Bob Cox, Tom Harp, George Hill, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03495)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, Freshman team, 1969 (Box 28, Item UA13020018-N-03496)
    - Leo Hart, Wes Chesson, two unidentified females (color), 1970 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03497)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1970 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03498)
    - Coaches' Wives, unidentified, 1970 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03499)
    - Trainers, unidentified, 1970 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03500)
    - Coaches, Freshman team, unidentified, 1970 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03501)
    - Managerial Staff, unidentified, 1970 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03502)
    - Players, unidentified groupings, Freshman team, 1971 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03503)
    - Players, unidentified, Press Day, 1972 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03504)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified (color), 1972 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03505)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1972 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03506)
    - Coaches and their Families, unidentified, 1972 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03507)
    - Trainers, unidentified, 1972 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03508)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified (color), 1973 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03509)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, Freshman team, 1973 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03510)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1973 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03511)
    - Secretaries, unidentified, 1973 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03512)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified (color), 1974 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03513)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1974 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03514)
    - Players, Freshman Recruits, unidentified, 1976 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03515)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1976 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03516)
    - Coaching Staff and Families, unidentified, 1976 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03517)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1977 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03518)
    - Players, unidentified, 1978 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03519)
    - Trainers [?], unidentified, 1978 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03520)
    - Trainers [?], unidentified, 1978 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03521)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified (color), 1980-1981 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03522)
    - Coaching Staff, unidentified, 1980 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03523)
    - Co-Captains, unidentified, 1981 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03524)
    - Seniors, unidentified, 1988 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03525)
    - Seniors, unidentified (color), 1990 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03526)
    - Players, unidentified, posed on Duke Chapel stairs (color), circa 1990s (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03527)
    - Players, unidentified, undated (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03528)
    - Coaching Staff, Freshman team, unidentified, undated (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03529)
  - Teams, 30
    - Team, 1891 (copy negative), undated (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03530)
    - Team, 1900 (copy negative), undated (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03531)
    - Team, 1927, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05697)
    - Team, Freshman, 1929, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05698)
    - Team, 1929, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05699)
    - Team, Freshman, 1930, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05700)
    - Team, 1931 (copy negative), 1967 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03532)
    - Team, Freshman, 1932, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05701)
    - Team, 1932, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05702)
    - Team, 1933, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05703)
    - Team, 1933 Squad outside U. S. Capitol (copy negative), 1973 Oct. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03533)
    - Team, Freshman, 1934, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05704)
    - Team, 1934 (copy negative), 1967 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03534)
    - Team, Freshman, 1935, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05705)
    - Team, 1935, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05706)
    - Team, Freshman, 1936, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05707)
    - Team, 1936 (copy negative), 1967 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03535)
    - Team, Freshman, 1937, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05708)
    - Team, 1937, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05709)
    - Team, Freshman, 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05710)
    - Team, Freshman, 1938 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03536)
    - Team, 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05711)
    - Team, 1939, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05712)
    - Team, 1939 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03537)
    - Team, Freshman, 1940, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05713)
    - Team, 1940 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03538)
    - Team, 1941 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03539)
    - Team, Rose Bowl Squad, 1941, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05714)
    - Team, Rose Bowl Squad, 1941 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03540)
    - Team, 1942 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03541)
    - Team, 1943, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05715)
    - Team, White Squad, 1943 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03542)
    - Team, Blue Squad, 1943, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05716)
    - Team, 1944, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05717)
    - Team, White Squad, 1944, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05718)
    - Team, Sugar Bowl Squad, 1944, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05719)
    - Team, White Squad, 1945, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05720)
    - Team, 1945, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05721)
    - Team, 1945 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03543)
    - Team, 1946, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05722)
    - Team, Blue Squad, 1946 Sept. 7, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05723)
    - Team, Blue Squad, 1946 Sept. 7 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03544)
    - Team, White Squad, 1946 Sept. 7, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05724)
    - Team, White Squad, 1946 Sept. 7 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03545)
    - Team, 1947, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05725)
    - Team, "B" Team (varsity), 1947 Sept. 11 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03546)
    - Team, Freshman, 1948 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03547)
    - Team, 1948, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05726)
    - Team, 1948 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03548)
    - Team, 1949 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03549)
    - Team, Freshman, 1950 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03550)
    - Team, 1950 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03551)
    - Team, 1952 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03552)
    - Team, Freshman, 1953 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03553)
    - Team, 1953 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03554)
    - Team, 1954 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03555)
    - Team, Freshman, 1955 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03556)
    - Team, 1955 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03557)
    - Team, Freshman, 1956 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03558)
    - Team, 1956 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03559)
    - Team, Freshman, 1957 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03560)
    - Team, 1957 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03561)
    - Team, Orange Bowl Team, Press Day, 1957 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03562)
    - Team, Orange Bowl Team, Press Day, 1957 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03563)
    - Team, Freshman, 1958 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03564)
    - Team, 1958 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03565)
    - Team, Freshman, 1959 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03566)
    - Team, 1959 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03567)
    - Team, Freshman, 1960 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03568)
    - Team, 1960 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03569)
    - Team, at 20th Century Fox Studios, California, 1960 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03570)
    - Team, at 20th Century Fox Studios, California, 1960 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03571)
    - Team, Freshman, 1961 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03572)
    - Team, 1961 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03573)
    - Team, 1961 Cotton Bowl Champs (copy negative), 1962 Feb. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03574)
    - Team, Freshman, 1962 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03575)
    - Team, 1962 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03576)
    - Team, Freshman, 1963 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03577)
    - Team, 1963 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03578)
    - Team, Varsity Groups, 1963 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03579)
    - Team, Varsity Groups, 1963 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03580)
    - Team, Varsity Groups, 1963 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03581)
    - Team, Varsity Groups, 1963 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03582)
    - Team, Freshman, 1964 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03583)
    - Team, 1964 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03584)
    - Team, Freshman, 1965 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03585)
    - Team, 1965 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03586)
    - Team, Freshman, 1966 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03587)
    - Team, 1966 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03588)
    - Team, Freshman, 1967 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03589)
    - Team, 1967 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03590)
    - Team, Offensive, 1967 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03591)
    - Team, Defensive, 1967 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03592)
    - Team, Freshman, 1968 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03593)
    - Team, 1968 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03594)
    - Team, 1969 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03595)
    - Team, Freshman, 1970 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03596)
    - Team, 1970 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03597)
    - Team, Freshman, 1971 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03598)
    - Team, 1971 (color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03599)
    - Team, 1971 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03600)
    - Team, Freshman, 1972 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03601)
    - Team, 1972 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03602)
    - Team, 1972 Aug. (color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03603)
    - Team, Freshman, 1973 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03604)
    - Team, 1973 Aug. (includes color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03605)
    - Team, Freshman, 1974 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03606)
    - Team, 1974 (includes color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03607)
    - Team, 1975 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03608)
    - Team, 1975 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03609)
    - Team, Freshman, 1976 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03610)
    - Team, 1976 (color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03611)
    - Team, 1976 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03612)
    - Team, 1977 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03613)
    - Team, 1978 Sept. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03614)
    - Team, 1978 (color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03615)
    - Team, 1979 (color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03616)
    - Team, 1979 Aug. (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03617)
    - Team, 1980 (includes color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03618)
    - Team, 1981 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03619)
    - Team, 1983 (color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03620)
    - Team, 1989 (color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03621)
    - Team, 1990 (color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03622)
    - Team, 1991 (color) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03623)
    - Team (Wake Forest cover, color), 1995 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03624)
    - Team, undated (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03625)
  - Games, 31
    - Duke vs. Davidson, 1930, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05727)
    - Duke vs. Davidson, 1930, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05728)
    - Duke vs. Navy, 1930, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05729)
    - Duke vs. NC State, 1934, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05730)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 1934, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05731)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1934, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05732)
    - Duke vs. Clemson, 1935, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05733)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1935, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05734)
    - Duke vs. Auburn, 1935, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05735)
    - Duke vs. Auburn, 1935, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05736)
    - Duke vs. Colgate, 1936, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05737)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 1936 Oct. 19, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05738)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1936, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05739)
    - Duke vs. Washington & Lee, 1936, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05740)
    - unidentified Games, 1937, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05741)
    - unidentified Games, 1937, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05742)
    - unidentified Games, 1937, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05743)
    - Practice Session, 1937 Sept. 1, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05744)
    - Practice Session, 1937 Sept. 1, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05745)
    - Practice Session, 1937 Sept. 1, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05746)
    - Duke vs. Wake Forest, 1937 Nov. 6, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05747)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1937 Nov. 13, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05748)
    - Duke vs. UNC, 1937 Nov. 13, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05749)
    - Duke vs. NC State, 1937 Nov. 20, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05750)
    - Duke vs. Pittsburgh, 1937 Nov. 27, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05751)
    - Pre-Season Practice, 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05752)
    - Pre-Season Practice, 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05753)
    - Pre-Season Practice, 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05754)
    - unidentified game, 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05755)
    - Duke Imps vs. NC State (Freshman teams), 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05756)
    - Duke Imps vs. NC State (Freshman teams), 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05757)
    - Practice in Preparation for Rose Bowl, 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05758)
    - Practice in Preparation for Rose Bowl, 1938, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05759)
    - Rose Bowl 1939 (copy negative of book/magazine cover) (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03626)
    - Rose Bowl Sidelights, 1939 Jan., Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05760)
    - Rose Bowl Sidelights, 1939 Jan., Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05761)
    - Rose Bowl Homecoming, 1939 Jan. 6, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05762)
    - unidentified Games, 1939, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05763)
    - unidentified Games, 1939 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03627)
    - unidentified Games, 1939 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03628)
    - unidentified Games, 1939 (Box 29, Item UA13020018-N-03629)
    - Duke vs. Clemson (spring practice), 1939 Mar. 18, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05764)
    - Fall Practice, 1939, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05765)
    - unidentified Games, 1940, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05766)
    - unidentified Games, 1940, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05767)
    - unidentified Games, 1940, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05768)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 1940 Nov. 2, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05769)
    - Duke vs. Georgia Tech, 1940 Nov. 2 (Box 30, Item UA13020018-N-03630)
    - Practice Sessions, 1941, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05770)
    - unidentified Games, 1941, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05771)
    - unidentified Games, 1941, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05772)
    - unidentified Games, 1941, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05773)
    - unidentified Games, 1941, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05774)
    - unidentified Games, 1941, Nitrate (Box 39, Item UA13020018-N-05775)